APOORV ABHISHEK

SDE - 2

apoorvabhishek2010@gmail.com

apoorvabhishek.com

**** 8989143106

9 Bengaluru

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/apoorvabhishek/

EDUCATION

Jaypee University
of Engineering and
Technology

Aug.
2013 to
June
2017

B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering with CGPA of 7.2

SUMMARY

Achievement-driven professional with an experience of 6 years in software development. Experienced in executing projects efficiently within time, budget and quality parameters as per best practices guidelines. Have ability to learn new things quickly and thoroughly.

I consider myself a self starter as well as an outstanding team player. I am also an effective communicator with strong networking and client engagement skills.

SKILLS

CORE - COMPETENCIES: Python, Django, OOP, Data Structures

TECHNOLOGY EXPERTISE: Docker, Linux, Kubernetes, Openshift, Azure, AWS

EMPLOYMENT

AMADEUS SOFTWARE LABS

Software Development Engineer - 2

INFOSYS LIMITED

Technology Analyst

Bengaluru, India Mar. 2022 to Current

Bengaluru, India July 2017 to Mar. 2022

PROJECTS

COMPLEX REPORTING TOOL

Mar. 2022 to Current

The Django application maintains enormous database of all PTRs and WOs and displays customizable visualizations to the group owners. The app is a classic example of collection of all modern technology implementation which takes in account both robustness and scalability.

MAGNET Dec. 2020 to Mar. 2022

The projects tracks and monitors IOT devices on the field and processes data as per the requirements and expose them using APIs. Data is then available in the form of WebApp to the end users.

UNSTRUCTURED DATA ANALYTICS PLATFORM

Jan. 2019 to Dec. 2020

The project was aimed to create an application which can store the meta data and extracted data from files at multiple storage locations and classify them so as to make them meaningful and easily accessible to end users using a webApp. The app used to monitor the location continuously.

DATA PROCESSING USING PYTHON

July 2017 to Dec. 2018

Worked on Data Processing Application which involved a series of incoming data which needed to be processed as per client's requirements and produce Selective Output.

AWARDS

Infosys Limited · MOST VALUABLE PLAYER AWARD

Nov. 2021

For quick and quality delivery of product

Infosys Limited · HACKATHON

Mar. 2020

An ML tool was developed to classify petroleum log files.

Infosys Limited · MOST VALUABLE PLAYER AWARD

Apr. 2019

For quality work delivery